{
    "title": "Hockey",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "What NHL player was given the nickname The Roadrunner?",
            "choices": [
                "Maurice Richard",
                "Phil Housley",
                "Al Maclnnis",
                "Yvan Cournoyer"
            ],
            "answer": 3
        },
        {
            "question": "Who was the first-ever goaltender to be a captain in the NHL?",
            "choices": [
                "George Hainsworth",
                "Alex Connell",
                "Roy Worters",
                "John Ross Roach"
            ],
            "answer": 3
        },
        {
            "question": "Which two NHL teams faced off in a preseason game in London in 1992?",
            "choices": [
                "Montreal Canadiens vs. Vancouver Canucks",
                "Detroit Red Wings vs. New York Rangers",
                "Chicago Blackhawks vs. Montreal Canadiens",
                "Toronto Maple Leafs vs. Boston Bruins"
            ],
            "answer": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Who is the Conn Smythe Trophy awarded to?",
            "choices": [
                "Best goalie",
                "Most valuable player to his team during the playoffs",
                "Rookie of the year",
                "Player with the most goals in the season"
            ],
            "answer": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Who was traded to Vancouver from Florida in the 2005-06 offseason?",
            "choices": [
                "Mike Ribeiro",
                "Anson Carter",
                "Roberto Luongo",
                "Brent Sopel"
            ],
            "answer": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "In the 1993-94 season, who did the Vancouver Canucks lose to in the Stanley Cup finals?",
            "choices": [
                "New York Islanders",
                "New York Rangers",
                "Boston Bruins",
                "Montreal Canadiens"
            ],
            "answer": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "In the 2005 NHL entry draft, what player was drafted 1st round, 21st overall by the Toronto Maple Leafs?",
            "choices": [
                "Jakub Kindl",
                "Alex Bourret",
                "Ryan O'marra",
                "Tuukka Rask"
            ],
            "answer": 3
        },
        {
            "question": "In 1966-67, what team won the Stanley Cup?",
            "choices": [
                "Montreal Canadiens",
                "Toronto Maple Leafs",
                "Chicago Blackhawks",
                "Boston Bruins"
            ],
            "answer": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Who was left winger Taylor Pyatt drafted by in the 1999 NHL entry draft?",
            "choices": [
                "Buffalo Sabres",
                "New York Islanders",
                "Vancouver Canucks",
                "Montreal Canadiens"
            ],
            "answer": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Who was the first player to ever win the Hart Trophy?",
            "choices": [
                "Eddie Shore",
                "Billy Burch",
                "Frank Nighbor",
                "Howie Morenz"
            ],
            "answer": 2
        }
    ]
}